Xavier University Higher Learning Commission accreditation records
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections
- Higher Learning Commission/ North Central Association Visit of April 4-6 2011 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  In this folder: 1. "Report of a Comprehensive Evaluation Visit to Xavier University, April 4-6, 2011, for the Higher Learning Commission (includes the Assurance Section and the Advancement Section). 2. A comprehensive list of all the documents made available to the HLC visiting team, both in electronic form (digital Resource Room) and in print form (Physical Resource Room). 3. A flash drive containing all the documents in the Digital Resource Room (which documents have been copied to the Archives permanent storage drive). 4. A letter to President Graham from HLC extending Xavier's accreditation to Columbia Center, Fort Mitchell, Kentucky (dated 3/24/2011)
- Higher Learning Commission/ North Central Association Visit of April 4-6, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  In this folder: The Xavier University HLC Self-Study for 2011.
- Higher Learning Commission/ North Central Association Visit of April 4-6, 2011, 2009-2010; undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  In this folder: 1. Preparing for a Team Visit/ Self Study Design. 2. Mission Statements of the Academic Departments. 3. Letters of authorization from the Ohio Board of Regents. 4. Accreditation Visit: Radiologic Technology Program, January 2010. 5. Reports from the National Survey of Student Engagement (NSEE) for Xavier University.
- Higher Learning Commission/ North Central Association Visit of April 4-6, 2011, 2008-2011; undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  This folder contains the documents produced for the HLC visitors concerning federal compliance requirements. For a list of these requirements see the "Report of a Comprehensive Evaluation Visit to Xavier University, Assurance Section;" Part VI, Appendix: Federal Compliance Requirements.
- Higher Learning Commission/ North Central Association Visit of April 4-6, 2011, 2010-2011; undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  In this folder: Materials pertaining to Program Assessment Planning and Assessment Management.